Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1969-1993; Accession 1999-A-091
  - Tusek BR68A Fall 1976 (Box 10, Folder 436)
  - Tallmadge JE79A (Box 10, Folder 437)
  - Steel CSJE/CSCC 97b (Box 10, Folder 438)
  - White JE78A (Box 10, Folder 439)
  - Astrachan PC82A (Box 10, Folder 440)
  - Ryan PC77A (Box 10, Folder 441)
  - Bromwich PC78A (Box 10, Folder 442)
  - Stave SY81A (Box 10, Folder 443)
  - D, Ryan SY80A (Box 10, Folder 444)
  - Kettl SY82A (Box 10, Folder 445)
  - Cornwell SM87A (Box 10, Folder 446)
  - G. Martin SM83A (Box 10, Folder 447)
  - Woolington SM82A (Box 10, Folder 448)
  - Kalilna SM79A (Box 10, Folder 449)
  - Parks-- SM workshop (Box 10, Folder 450)
  - Parks-- SM workshop (Box 10, Folder 451)
  - Moran ES78A (Box 10, Folder 452)
  - Healey ES74A (Box 10, Folder 453)
  - Rothchild (Box 10, Folder 454)
  - Warren and Wilhelm TC 83A (Box 10, Folder 455)
  - Eiseman TC 80A (Box 10, Folder 456)
  - Jonathan Edwards Spring 1977 Budgets & Costs (Box 10, Folder 457)
  - Paul CSJE 91b (Box 10, Folder 458)
  - Diggory CS JE89b (Box 10, Folder 459)
  - Hammond CS JE/ CS JC 88b (Box 10, Folder 460)
  - Resnick CSJE 93b (Box 10, Folder 461)
  - Smith MC65A (Box 10, Folder 462)
  - Davis, Workshop CSUC (Box 10, Folder 463)
  - Langer CSMC 79b (Box 10, Folder 464)
  - Glasgow- Winter CSPC/ BK90A (Box 10, Folder 465)
  - Warsito, workshop CSPC (Box 10, Folder 466)
  - Uviller-- CSPC/ CSSY85b (Box 10, Folder 467)
  - Rena Uviller CSCC 44b/ CSSM 44b (Box 10, Folder 468)
  - Stoff/ Seron CSPC/ CSTD86b (Box 10, Folder 469)
  - Lucid CSPC/ CSSY89b (Box 10, Folder 470)
  - Vise/ Tear CSSY 88b (Box 10, Folder 471)
  - Joki CSSY89b (Box 10, Folder 472)
  - Mink CSES 92b (Box 10, Folder 473)
  - Manor ES80b (Box 10, Folder 474)
  - Benedetto ES77A (Box 10, Folder 475)
  - Bregstein CSES 89b (Box 10, Folder 476)
  - Johnson CSES 86b (Box 10, Folder 477)
  - Tandy CSTC 97b (Box 10, Folder 478)
  - Hsia CSCC/ CSSY 95b (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - Taylor CC 84A (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - Silber & Post CC/PC 53A (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - Garet CSBK 83A/ CSCC 83b (Box 11, Folder 482)
  - Fleishmann-Winer BR 71A (Box 11, Folder 483)
  - Adler BR 70A (Box 11, Folder 484)
  - Hawes CC 86A (Box 11, Folder 485)
  - Durk CCSY 63b (Box 11, Folder 486)
  - A. Bloom CC 42b/ SM 42b (Box 11, Folder 487)
  - Brown CSES 72b (Box 11, Folder 488)
  - Trumbull Spring 1976 Budgets and Costs (Box 11, Folder 489)
  - Magee et. al. TC/ CC 66A+b (Box 11, Folder 490)
  - Wilson CSTC 70b (Box 11, Folder 491)
  - Wilson CSSY 20b (Box 11, Folder 492)
  - Elkins CSTC 71b (Box 11, Folder 493)
  - Rout, CSES 64b (Box 11, Folder 494)
  - Bloom CSES/ CSSM 42b (Box 11, Folder 495)
  - Haiko ES 51A (Box 11, Folder 496)
  - Jonathan Pincus ES 11b (Box 11, Folder 497)
  - Howe, CSES 68b (Box 11, Folder 498)
  - Peter Steiner CSES 65b (Box 11, Folder 499)
  - Pincus CSES 66b (Box 11, Folder 500)
  - Ezra Stiles Spring 1976: Budgets & Costs (Box 11, Folder 501)
  - Bates. CCSM workshop (Box 11, Folder 502)
  - Wendy Steiner CSES 48b (Box 11, Folder 503)
  - Levine CSSM 64b (Box 11, Folder 504)
  - McClatchy CSSM 65b (Box 11, Folder 505)
  - Findly CSSM 72b/ CSJE 72b (Box 11, Folder 506)
  - Giles CSSM 70b/ CSJE 70b (Box 11, Folder 507)
  - Silliman Spring 1976: Budgets & Costs (Box 11, Folder 508)
  - Heinen, CSSY 65b (Box 11, Folder 509)
  - Galambos CSSY 18b (Box 11, Folder 510)
  - Peter Johnson SY 29A (Box 11, Folder 511)
  - Johnson CSSY 60b (Box 11, Folder 512)
  - Warren/ Wilhelm CSTC 83b (Box 11, Folder 513)
  - BenhabibCSBR 52b (Box 11, Folder 514)
  - BenhabibCSTC/ CSPC 96b (Box 11, Folder 515)
  - Webster CSTC/ CSBK 95b (Box 11, Folder 516)
  - Loope CSTC/ CSDC 89b (Box 11, Folder 517)
  - Loope CSTC/ CSDC 68b (Box 11, Folder 518)
  - Jorge Dominiquez BK (Box 11, Folder 519)
  - Spring 1977 Marshman CSMC (rejected) (Box 11, Folder 520)
  - Spring 1977 Wilcox CSCC (withdrawn) (Box 11, Folder 521)
  - Spring 1977 Weingarten CSCC (rejected) (Box 11, Folder 522)
  - Szabo- Peloczi CSBK 64b (Box 11, Folder 523)
  - Alexander CSBK 87b (Box 11, Folder 524)
  - McCoy CSBK 88b/ CSSM 88b (Box 11, Folder 525)
  - Branford College Spring 1977: Budgets & Costs (Box 11, Folder 526)
  - M. Winer ES 36b (Box 11, Folder 527)
  - Jordon CSBR/ CSJE 83b (Box 11, Folder 528)
  - Constance Kidd (Jordon) DC 36A (Box 11, Folder 529)
  - Irving CSBR 75b1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 530)
  - Goldman CSBR 91b (Box 11, Folder 531)
  - Parks CSBR 77b (Box 11, Folder 532)
  - Foltz CSBR 78b (Box 11, Folder 533)
  - Johnson CSBR 76b (Box 11, Folder 534)
  - de Solla Price CSCC / CSTD 92b (Box 11, Folder 535)
  - Grosse CSCC bworkshop (Box 11, Folder 536)
  - Waite CC workshop (Box 11, Folder 537)
  - Bergman ES 49A (Box 12, Folder 538)
  - Adams MC 66A (Box 12, Folder 539)
  - Fagin CSMC 38b (Box 12, Folder 540)
  - Gilbert/ Houtrides CSTC/ CSTD 74A (Box 12, Folder 541)
  - Klotz JE 59A (Box 12, Folder 542)
  - Insdorf MC DC JE 67bAM 76b (Box 12, Folder 543)
  - Insdorf PC 80A (Box 12, Folder 544)
  - Insdorf MC 26A (Box 12, Folder 545)
  - Bergman ES 76 A (Box 12, Folder 546)
  - Ross TC 81A (Box 12, Folder 547)
  - Divine BR 47A (Box 12, Folder 548)
  - Divine CSDC 64b (Box 12, Folder 549)
  - Peck & Barnes ES 73A (Box 12, Folder 550)
  - Silber CC 79A (Box 12, Folder 551)
  - Jackson CSCC CSTD 91b (Box 12, Folder 552)
  - Arkin CSDC 86b (Box 12, Folder 553)
  - Natanson CSDC 85b (Box 12, Folder 554)
  - Cahn CSCC/ CSPC 100A (Box 12, Folder 555)
  - Reider CSPC/ CSCC 110A (Box 12, Folder 556)
  - Klaic DC 68A (Box 12, Folder 557)
  - Lapin DC 73A (Box 12, Folder 558)
  - Lanford DC 80A (Box 12, Folder 559)
  - Watson DC 71A (Box 12, Folder 560)
  - Moore CSDC/ CSCC 88b (Box 12, Folder 561)
  - S. Moore BR 67A/ SY 67A (Box 12, Folder 562)
  - Moore CSDC 66b/ CSSE 66b (Box 12, Folder 563)
  - Moore SM 54A (Box 12, Folder 564)
  - Daniel Croft CSSY/ JE 19b (Box 12, Folder 565)
  - Wayne TD 76A (Box 12, Folder 566)
  - Fernandez TD 59A (Box 12, Folder 567)
  - Kiechel TD 61A (Box 12, Folder 568)
  - Bywaters CSTD 93b (Box 12, Folder 569)
  - Abelson TD60A (Box 12, Folder 570)
  - Berger CSTD 95b (Box 12, Folder 571)
  - Brown CSCC 89b (Box 12, Folder 572)
  - Haltunnen CSBR Fall 1977 (Box 12, Folder 573)
  - Davidson CSTC 122b (Box 12, Folder 574)
  - Krasin CSPC 103A Fall 1977 (Box 12, Folder 575)
  - Droge CSCC/ CSMC Fall 1977 (Box 12, Folder 576)
  - Walzar CSDC Fall 1977 (Box 12, Folder 577)
  - Burkot CSTC Fall 1977 (Box 12, Folder 578)
  - Adams/ Ginsberg CSES 105A Fall 1977 (Box 12, Folder 579)
  - Hafrey CSBK 100A (Box 12, Folder 580)
  - deMacedo CSBK 101b (Box 12, Folder 581)
  - Needler CSBK 102A (Box 12, Folder 582)
  - Kirkland CSBK 103A (Box 12, Folder 583)
  - Zahler CSBR 100A (Box 12, Folder 584)
  - Ayengar CSBR 102A (Box 12, Folder 585)
  - Lears CSCC/ CSDC 103A (Box 12, Folder 586)
  - Lapham CSCC/ CSSM 109A (Box 12, Folder 587)
  - Lewis CSCC/ CSPC 117b (Box 12, Folder 588)
  - Leitch CSCC/ CSMC 105A (Box 12, Folder 589)
  - Goldberger CSCC/ CSBR 107A (Box 12, Folder 590)
  - Sundaram CSDC/ CSTC 102A (Box 12, Folder 591)
  - Kleber/ Mandel CSDC 105A (Box 12, Folder 592)
  - Bahti CSDC 100A/ CSSY (Box 12, Folder 593)
  - Peck & Barnes CSDC 107A (Box 12, Folder 594)
  - Hazeltine CSDC/ CSBR 104A (Box 12, Folder 595)
  - Ruggles CSJE 105A (Box 12, Folder 596)
  - Oberle CSTD 104A (Box 12, Folder 597)
  - Wessel CSTD 101A (Box 12, Folder 598)
  - Winkler CSTD 100A (Box 12, Folder 599)
  - Turk CSJE 100A (Box 12, Folder 600)
  - Lucid CSJE 106A (Box 12, Folder 601)
  - Gordon CSCC 108A (Box 13, Folder 602)
  - Scott CSMC 101A (Box 13, Folder 603)
  - Fagin CSMC 103A (Box 13, Folder 604)
  - Steele CSPC 104A (Box 13, Folder 605)
  - Insdorf CSPC/ CSTD 102A (Box 13, Folder 606)
  - Clark/ Burch CSPC/ CSTD 108A (Box 13, Folder 607)
  - Dellinger CSPC 105A (Box 13, Folder 608)
  - Philipson CSSY 191A (Box 13, Folder 609)
  - Rizopoulos CSSY 106A (Box 13, Folder 610)
  - Richards CSSY 103A (Box 13, Folder 611)
  - Victor CSSM 103A (Box 13, Folder 612)
  - Laguna CSSM/ CSMC 104A (Box 13, Folder 613)
  - Elkus CSSM 100A (Box 13, Folder 614)
  - Klotz CSES 100A (Box 13, Folder 615)
  - Billington CSES Fall 1977 (Box 13, Folder 616)
  - Meeks CSES/ CSCC 104A (Box 13, Folder 617)
  - Crittenden CSES Fall 1977 (Box 13, Folder 618)
  - Singleton CSTC/ CSBK 104A (Box 13, Folder 619)
  - Houtrides CSTC 101A (Box 13, Folder 620)
  - Kirkland CSBK 111b (Box 13, Folder 621)
  - Barrow CSBK/ CSCC 112b (Box 13, Folder 622)
  - Whittaker CSBK 114b (Box 13, Folder 623)
  - Whittaker CSJE rejected (Box 13, Folder 624)
  - Whittaker CSJE 101A (Box 13, Folder 625)
  - Jackson CSBK 115b (Box 13, Folder 626)
  - Hendricks CSBK 113b (Box 13, Folder 627)
  - Berrigan CSBR 112b (Box 13, Folder 628)
  - Zaidi CSBR/ CSCC 114b (Box 13, Folder 629)
  - Berwick/ Wetzler CSBR 117b (Box 13, Folder 630)
  - Seccombe CSBR 119b (Box 13, Folder 631)
  - Knoll CSBR 111b (Box 13, Folder 632)
  - Seymour CSBR 103A (Box 13, Folder 633)
  - Donner CSCC/ CSTC 119b (Box 13, Folder 634)
  - Elon CSCC 120b (Box 13, Folder 635)
  - Pearson, Barry CSCC/ CSJE 113b (Box 13, Folder 636)
  - Gornick CSDC 111b (Box 13, Folder 637)
  - Wheeler CSDC 114b (Box 13, Folder 638)
  - Vandenbrouke CSDC 116b (Box 13, Folder 639)
  - Divine CSDC 115b (Box 13, Folder 640)
  - Kosinski CSTD 114b (Box 13, Folder 641)
  - Stanley CSTD105b (Box 13, Folder 642)
  - Edelman CSTD 115b (Box 13, Folder 643)
  - Mattison CSTD 111b (Box 13, Folder 644)
  - Robbins CSTD 113b (Box 13, Folder 645)
  - Lubell CSTC 103A (Box 13, Folder 646)
  - Hertz CSTD 116b (Box 13, Folder 647)
  - Lieberman CSJE CSSY (Box 13, Folder 648)
  - Lieberman CSPC 133A (Box 13, Folder 649)
  - Fisk CSJE/ CSJE/ CSPC 124b (Box 13, Folder 650)
  - Bergman CSUC 112b (Box 13, Folder 651)
  - Ross CSUC/ CSTC 116b (Box 13, Folder 652)
  - Adams Workshop CSUC (Box 13, Folder 653)
  - Bohman CSUC 113b (Box 13, Folder 654)
  - Brown CSUC 119b (Box 13, Folder 655)
  - Delius CSPC/ CSUC 114b (Box 13, Folder 656)
  - Cherner DC 135A (no manilla folder) (Box 13, Folder 657)
  - Hood CSPC 118b (Box 14, Folder 658)
  - Saxe CSSY/ CSPC 112b (Box 14, Folder 659)
  - Jervis CSSY 114b (Box 14, Folder 660)
  - Guare CSSY 116b (Box 14, Folder 661)
  - Saybrook Spring 1977: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 662)
  - Rostow CSSM 118b (Box 14, Folder 663)
  - Wen CSSM 119b (Box 14, Folder 664)
  - Leger CSSY 92b (Box 14, Folder 665)
  - Danzig CSES 121b (Box 14, Folder 666)
  - Hack CSES 111b (Box 14, Folder 667)
  - Kruger CSES 115b (Box 14, Folder 668)
  - Delius CSES 116b (Box 14, Folder 669)
  - Stein CSES 117b (Box 14, Folder 670)
  - Crittenden CSES 120b (Box 14, Folder 671)
  - Klotz CSSY 84b (Box 14, Folder 672)
  - Stowe CSES 119b (Box 14, Folder 673)
  - Snyder CSES 118b (Box 14, Folder 674)
  - (Snyder) (Box 14, Folder 675)
  - Garrison CSTC/ CSSY 120b (Box 14, Folder 676)
  - Garrison CSCC/ CSBR 94b (Box 14, Folder 677)
  - Isbin CSTC REPEAT (Box 14, Folder 678)
  - Ibsin CSMC/ CSTC b (Box 14, Folder 679)
  - Ramicova CSTC 121b (Box 14, Folder 680)
  - Trumbull workshop (Box 14, Folder 681)
  - McKinsey CSTC 110b (Box 14, Folder 682)
  - Louis Gilbert & Rene Houtrides TD 44b (Box 14, Folder 683)
  - Knoll CSBK 110b (Box 14, Folder 684)
  - Gordon CSMC 115b (Box 14, Folder 685)
  - McColl CSBR 116b (Box 14, Folder 686)
  - Berkeley Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 687)
  - Branford Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 688)
  - Calhoun Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 689)
  - Davenport Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 690)
  - Timothy Dwight Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 691)
  - Jonathan Edwards Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 692)
  - Morse Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 693)
  - Pierson Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 694)
  - Saybrook Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 695)
  - Ezra Stiles Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 696)
  - Trumbull Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 697)
  - Silliman Spring 1978: Budgets and Costs (Box 14, Folder 698)
  - Gurewitsch CSBR 131A (Box 14, Folder 699)
  - Pollak CSTD 134A (Box 14, Folder 700)
  - Pollak CSTD 90b (Box 14, Folder 701)
  - Deltete CSJE/ CSBR 133A (Box 14, Folder 702)
  - Cherner CSDC 135A (Box 14, Folder 703)
  - Grdseloff CSDC/ CSES 130A (Box 14, Folder 704)
  - Fabian CSPC 139A (Box 14, Folder 705)
  - Fradkin CSSM 106A (Box 15, Folder 706)
  - Bernstein CSMC Fall 1977 (Box 15, Folder 707)
  - Lesser CSMC 132A (Box 15, Folder 708)
  - Lesser MC 64A (Box 15, Folder 709)
  - Brokaw CSMC 134A (Box 15, Folder 710)
  - Most CSMC 130A (Box 15, Folder 711)
  - Tamarkin CSMC 133A (Box 15, Folder 712)
  - Bernstein CSUC 131A Fall 1978 (Box 15, Folder 713)
  - Bernstein CSBK 132A (Box 15, Folder 714)
  - Ostrom CSPC 136A (Box 15, Folder 715)
  - Segall CSPC140A (Box 15, Folder 716)
  - Lyons CSPC (Box 15, Folder 717)
  - Wessels CSPC/ CSDC 134A (Box 15, Folder 718)
  - Starr CSSY 133A (Box 15, Folder 719)
  - Myrans CSSY 130A (Box 15, Folder 720)
  - Reeve CSSY 81A REPEAT (Box 15, Folder 721)
  - Gralla Pierson workshop REPEAT (Box 15, Folder 722)
  - Macaulay CSSY 138A (Box 15, Folder 723)
  - Fox CSSM 131A (Box 15, Folder 724)
  - Fox SM77A (Box 15, Folder 725)
  - Crist CSSM 130A (Box 15, Folder 726)
  - Northshield CSSM 133A (Box 15, Folder 727)
  - White CSSM 132A (Box 15, Folder 728)
  - Rachootin CSES 131A (Box 15, Folder 729)
  - Holahan CSES 132A (Box 15, Folder 730)
  - Rudnytsky CSES/ CSJE 135A (Box 15, Folder 731)
  - Brecher ES 70A (Box 15, Folder 732)
  - Garey & Wright CSTC 132A (Box 15, Folder 733)
  - Miles CSTC CSTD 135A (Box 15, Folder 734)
  - Wheeler CSTC 136A (Box 15, Folder 735)
  - Tally CSTC 133A (Box 15, Folder 736)
  - Lermore CSCC CSPC 131A (Box 15, Folder 737)
  - Dale Roylance JE 34A (Box 15, Folder 738)
  - Levine CSBK 131A (Box 15, Folder 739)
  - Korner CSBK 130A (Box 15, Folder 740)
  - Biggs CSSM/ CSJE 134A (Box 15, Folder 741)
  - Biggs DC 46A (Box 15, Folder 742)
  - Solomon CSBR 132A (Box 15, Folder 743)
  - John McCrills (Box 15, Folder 744)
  - Hargrove CSCC 133A (Box 15, Folder 745)
  - Palmer CSCC/ CSPC 130A (Box 15, Folder 746)
  - Becton CSDC/ CSBR 137A (Box 15, Folder 747)
  - Mann CSDC/ CSBK 133A (Box 15, Folder 748)
  - White CSDC 136A (Box 15, Folder 749)
  - Kliman DC 49A REPEAT (Box 15, Folder 750)
  - (Paperella CSBR 134A) (Box 16, Folder 751)
  - Isay CSTD 131A (Box 16, Folder 752)
  - Buckingham CSTD 133A (Box 16, Folder 753)
  - Jablonski CSTD 130A (Box 16, Folder 754)
  - Rosenthal CSTD 132A (Box 16, Folder 755)
  - Goldsmith CSJE/ CSCC 137A (Box 16, Folder 756)
  - Powledge CSJE 131A (Box 16, Folder 757)
  - Powledge CSJE 102A (Box 16, Folder 758)
  - Morse College Spring 1979 Budgets & Costs (Box 16, Folder 759)
  - Klein CSMC 146b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 760)
  - Brown CSMC 141b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 761)
  - Mitchell CSMC 145b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 762)
  - Reilly CSMC 142b/ ES 142b (Box 16, Folder 763)
  - Reilly & Furth CSMC/ CSCC 121b (Box 16, Folder 764)
  - Isbin CSMC 144b/ TC 144b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 765)
  - Bernstein CSMC 163A Fall 1979 (Box 16, Folder 766)
  - Pierson College Spring 1979: Budgets & Costs (Box 16, Folder 767)
  - Waith CSPC 145b (Box 16, Folder 768)
  - Toombs CSPC 149b (Box 16, Folder 769)
  - Byck CSPC 153b (Box 16, Folder 770)
  - Robert Byck PC 44b (Box 16, Folder 771)
  - Lyons CSPC 148b (Box 16, Folder 772)
  - Casey CSPC 147b (Box 16, Folder 773)
  - Saybrook College: Spring 1979 (Box 16, Folder 774)
  - Waugh CSSY 141b (Box 16, Folder 775)
  - Fradkin CSSY 144b (Box 16, Folder 776)
  - Travis CSSY 140b (Box 16, Folder 777)
  - Wallace CSSY 142b (Box 16, Folder 778)
  - Reeve CSSY 11b (Box 16, Folder 779)
  - Silliman College Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 16, Folder 780)
  - Procaccini CSSM/ CSCC 136A (Box 16, Folder 781)
  - Essig CSSM 143 b/ TC 143b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 782)
  - Orland CSSM 146b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 783)
  - Lawson CSSM 140b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 784)
  - Slobin CSSM 145b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 785)
  - Chodos CSSM 141b1978- 1979 (Box 16, Folder 786)
  - Ezra Stiles Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 16, Folder 787)
  - Wilentz CSES 143b (Box 16, Folder 788)
  - Grosholtz CSES 144b (Box 16, Folder 789)
  - Breecher CSTC 123b (Box 16, Folder 790)
  - Miles CSTC 114b (Box 16, Folder 791)
  - Trumbull College Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 16, Folder 792)
  - Tally CSTC CSCC 112A (Box 16, Folder 793)
  - Levmore CSTC 145b (Box 16, Folder 794)
  - Prelinger CSTC 142b (Box 16, Folder 795)
  - Prelinger TC/ BR 48A REPEAT (Box 16, Folder 796)
  - Roylance CSTC 141b (Box 16, Folder 797)
  - Berkeley: Budgets & Costs Sp 1977 (Box 16A, Folder 798)
  - Committee on Teaching Faculty Meeting 1978 (no manilla folder) (Box 16A, Folder 799)
  - Smith Memoes 1975- 1976 (Box 16A, Folder 800)
  - Teaching in the Residential Colleges: Grading (Box 16A, Folder 801)
  - Committee on Teaching Minutes 1977- 1978 (blue book) (Box 16A, Folder 802)
  - CTRC Report (Box 16A, Folder 803)
  - (Scores of unlabelled, loose papers without folders, but all related to the CTRC (Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges) (Box 16A, Folder 804)
  - Tarasulo CSJE 141b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 805)
  - Barowski CSTD 145b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 806)
  - Loope CSBK 146bSpring 1979 (Box 17, Folder 807)
  - Apfelbaum CSBK 143b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 808)
  - Pearson CSDC 147b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 809)
  - Cherner CSDC 113b (Box 17, Folder 810)
  - Potter CSSM 142b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 811)
  - Potter CSPC 116b (Box 17, Folder 812)
  - Ranalli CSMC 143b78-79 (Box 17, Folder 813)
  - Rochelle CSBR 144b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 814)
  - Weaver CSJE 143b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 815)
  - Duesing CSJE (Box 17, Folder 816)
  - Berkeley College Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 17, Folder 817)
  - Biggs CSBK 150b/ CSPC 150b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 818)
  - Biggs CSJE 112b (Box 17, Folder 819)
  - Crawley CSBK 140b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 820)
  - Branford Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 17, Folder 821)
  - Reid CSBR 146b (Box 17, Folder 822)
  - Strawbridge CSBR 145b (Box 17, Folder 823)
  - Shoaf CSBR 143b (Box 17, Folder 824)
  - Calhoun Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 17, Folder 825)
  - McCrillis CSCC 147b (Box 17, Folder 826)
  - Wilcox CSCC 150b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 827)
  - Medley CSCC 145b (Box 17, Folder 828)
  - Cook CSCC 151b (Box 17, Folder 829)
  - Kessen CSCC 146b (Box 17, Folder 830)
  - Appiah CSCC 149b (Box 17, Folder 831)
  - Davenport Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 17, Folder 832)
  - Lustig CSDC 143b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 833)
  - Poveymirov CSTD 144b (Box 17, Folder 834)
  - Hahn/ Weinstein CSDC 144b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 835)
  - Hahn/ Weinstein CSDC 112b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 836)
  - Hahn/ Weinstein CSMC 54b (Box 17, Folder 837)
  - Rubin CSDC 142b/ CSBR 142b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 838)
  - Kliman CSDC 146b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 839)
  - Kliman CSDC 90b (Box 17, Folder 840)
  - Goodich CSDC 141b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 841)
  - Schiffrin CSDC 140b/ CSTC 140b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 842)
  - Schiffrin CSDC 87b (Box 17, Folder 843)
  - Timothy Dwight Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 17, Folder 844)
  - Buckingham CSTD 88b (Box 17, Folder 845)
  - Faculty Meeting: Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges (no manilla folder) (Box 17, Folder 846)
  - Levbsdorf CSTD 143b (Box 17, Folder 847)
  - Schiff CSTD 146b (Box 17, Folder 848)
  - Douglas CSTD 141b (Box 17, Folder 849)
  - Jonathan Edwards Spring 1979: Budgets and Costs (Box 17, Folder 850)
  - Pollina CSJE 140b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 851)
  - Gill CSJE 146b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 852)
  - Weiss CSJE 148b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 853)
  - Chace CSJE 111b (Box 17, Folder 854)
  - Chace CSJE 142b/ PC/ 142b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 855)
  - James Chace JE 94b (Box 17, Folder 856)
  - Chace CSJE 48b (Box 17, Folder 857)
  - Brown CSJE 145b/ SY 145b1978- 1979 (Box 17, Folder 858)
  - Hazard/ Wellman CSCC/ CSES 166A (Fall 1979) (Box 18, Folder 859)
  - Frazier CSCC/ CSPC 165A (Fall 1979) (Box 18, Folder 860)
  - Paparella CSBR 157A (Box 18, Folder 861)
  - Taylor CSMC/ CSES 156A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 862)
  - Taylor CSMC 135A (Box 18, Folder 863)
  - Cameron CSMC 155A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 864)
  - Levine CSMC 159A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 865)
  - Rabkin CSUC 160A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 866)
  - Flyth CSMC 162A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 867)
  - Wright CSUC 161A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 868)
  - Fitzgerald CSPC/ CSCC 167A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 869)
  - Davis CSPC 157A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 870)
  - Perlis CSPC/ CSES 162A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 871)
  - Smith CSPC/ CSCC 168A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 872)
  - Stokes CSSY 156A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 873)
  - Ingalls CSSY 157A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 874)
  - Silliman College Spring 1980: Budgets and Costs (Box 18, Folder 875)
  - Ornston CSSY 167b (Box 18, Folder 876)
  - Collat CSSM 161 A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 877)
  - Beacham CSSY/ CSBK 160A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 878)
  - Giroud CSSM 157A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 879)
  - Freccero CSSM/ CSMC 158A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 880)
  - Valesio/ Paradiso CSSM 165b (Box 18, Folder 881)
  - Valesio CSSM 159A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 882)
  - Nelson CSCC/ CSBK 164A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 883)
  - Fitch CSSM 156A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 884)
  - Ventur CSSM 169b/ CSTD 169b (Box 18, Folder 885)
  - Holston CSSM 155A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 886)
  - Jones CSES 157A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 887)
  - Burns CSES 159A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 888)
  - Berenbaum CSES 160A (Box 18, Folder 889)
  - Metlitzke CSES 158A (Box 18, Folder 890)
  - Sewall CSES 164b (Box 18, Folder 891)
  - Trumbull College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 18, Folder 892)
  - Bennett CSTC 134A (Box 18, Folder 893)
  - Bennett TC/ PC 33A REPEAT (Box 18, Folder 894)
  - Fersch CSTC 130A (Box 18, Folder 895)
  - Fersch CSTC 159A (Box 18, Folder 896)
  - Fersch TC/ ES 63A (Box 18, Folder 897)
  - Freeman CSTC 156A (Box 18, Folder 898)
  - Alt CSTC 160A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 899)
  - Harvitz CSTC 158A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 900)
  - Nadel CSTC 162A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 901)
  - Asbell CSTC 155A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 902)
  - Fereston CSBK 157A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 903)
  - Gorsuch CSBK Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 904)
  - Bayne CSBK 156A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 905)
  - Field CSBK 158A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 906)
  - Reynolds 159A 1979- 1980 (Box 18, Folder 907)
  - Geffen CSBK workshop Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 908)
  - Geffen CSBK 134A (Box 18, Folder 909)
  - Geffen CSBK (Box 18, Folder 910)
  - Branford College Spring 1980: Costs (Box 18, Folder 911)
  - Morton CSBR 155A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 912)
  - Harding CSBR 162A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 913)
  - Longwell CSBR 158A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 914)
  - Carey CSBR 159A Fall 1979 (Box 18, Folder 915)
  - Wolf CSBR 156A Fall 1979 (Box 19, Folder 916)
  - Wolf CSBR 140bSpring 1979 (Box 19, Folder 917)
  - Wolf CSUC 80b (Box 19, Folder 918)
  - Licht & Lewis CSCC/ CSSY 160A Fall 1979 (Box 19, Folder 919)
  - Weyer CSCC/ CSPC 159A Fall 1979 (Box 19, Folder 920)
  - Brooks CSCC/ CSTC 157A Fall 1979 (Box 19, Folder 921)
  - Buxton CSCC/ CSPC 156A (Box 19, Folder 922)
  - Osterweis CSJE 156 A (Box 19, Folder 923)
  - Boyce/ Hartman CSBK 142b (Box 19, Folder 924)
  - Rabbi Wolf CSPC/ CSBK 74b (Box 19, Folder 925)
  - Shea CSDC 159A (Box 19, Folder 926)
  - Liebert CSDC 155A (Box 19, Folder 927)
  - Liebert DC/ JE 32A REPEAT (Box 19, Folder 928)
  - Kazemzadeh CSDC 157A (Box 19, Folder 929)
  - Howe CSDC/ CSCC 158A (Box 19, Folder 930)